manageprojects.com 2016-05-01

# Privacy Policy — Active Collab

We're a small company and we don't have a fancy privacy policy written in lawyerish. Instead, we'd like to let you know plain and simple on how we take care of your information. We promise we won't act outside of our privacy policy or misuse your data in any way. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will notify you on our website or via newsletter.

## We do:

  * Collect personal data that can't reveal your identity (such as browser type, language preference, referring site, date and time of each visit, request, etc).
  * Collect identifying personal information (like IP address, email, username, password, etc).
  * Put cookies1 in your browser.

## Why?

  * So that we can customize your each visit and make you feel at home on our website.
  * To better understand your needs and demands related to our products and services.
  * For our own market research purposes.

## We collect your data when you:

  * Visit our website.
  * Log in or sign up to our services.
  * Try our products.
  * Subscribe to our newsletter.
  * Join our community.
  * Post comments on our blogs.
  * Buy a software license.

## We don’t:

  * Sell any kind of personal information or data.
  * Disclose this information to other marketers or third parties.
  * Manipulate your data in any way, other than stated here.

## We protect your data by:

  * Taking administrative, technical, and physical measures of precaution.
  * Using SSL22 encryption.

## We might occasionally:

  * Release non-personally identifying information (eg. a report on our products and services).
  * Ask you to participate in a voluntary survey about our products.
  * Ask you to send us a testimonial.

1 Cookie – a string of information stored on a user’s computer by a website; the visitor’s browser then provides this information to the website on every returning visit.  
2 SSL – Secure Socket Layer
